Guide to the Gene Golub Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2008-159
  - Videocassettes:
    - Unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (Hi-8) (Box 10)
  - Audio & Data Media
    - An Interview with Jim Wilkinson, copy 1, 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 11)
    - An Interview with Jim Wilkinson, copy 2, 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 11)
    - Casablanca 10, 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 11)
    - Mathematics Department Software CD, August 2000, 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 11)
    - Ofer-Donabel Wedding Photos, 9/27/2003, 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 11)
    - Department of Computer Science, University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, 2005, 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 11)
    - Fields Medallists Lectures (Box 11)
    - G. Meurant-Numerical Methods for Large Linear Systems, 1999, 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 11)
    - In-Our-Time: Melvyn Bragg, 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 11)
    - QNAS program, 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 11)
    - Reprints of G. H. Golub, 1 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 11)
    - America Online, 1 computer disc (3 1/2") (Box 11)
    - Internet Apps + Mac TCP, 1 computer disc (3 1/2") (Box 11)
    - Printer Software Disk 2, 1 computer disc (3 1/2") (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 computer disc (3 1/2") (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 optical disc (MiniDisc) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 optical disc (MiniDisc) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 optical disc (MiniDisc) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 optical disc (MiniDisc) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 optical disc (MiniDisc) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 optical disc (MiniDisc) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 optical disc (MiniDisc) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 optical disc (MiniDisc) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 optical disc (MiniDisc) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 optical disc (MiniDisc) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 optical disc (MiniDisc) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 optical disc (MiniDisc) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 optical disc (MiniDisc) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette (Microcassette) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette (Microcassette) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette (Microcassette) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette (Microcassette) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette (Microcassette) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette (Microcassette) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette (Microcassette) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette (Microcassette) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette (Microcassette) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette (Microcassette) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette (Microcassette) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled [Flash] (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 optical disc (MiniDisc) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 optical disc (MiniDisc) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 optical disc (MiniDisc) (Box 11)
    - Evacuees, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - George Harrison-All Things Must Pass, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Dramatic Readings from O'Neill By Jason Robarts, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - After the Fall 5, 6 (Side A), After the Fall 7 & 8 (Side B), 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Bill Evans, "From Left to Right" (Side A), Bill Evans, "Alone" (Side B), 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Marshall Tucker Band "Where We All Belong", 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Paxman Nationalism, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Melvyn Bragg-Mind/Body (Side A), Eddie [Illegible] (Side B), 1999, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Paxman "Geography" (Side A), 6/12/1999, Belvyn Bragg, 1999 (Side B), 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Gore Vidal in Psych. chair. (Side A), Desert Island-Albee Sachs (Side B), 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Barbara Babcock "Women in Power" (Side A), 11/7/1979, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - "Frontiers" Pete Evans, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Witnesses to the Holocaust, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Terry Gross, Angela Houston, 3/8/2000, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Melvyn Bragg (Side A), Paxman (Side B), 2001, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Jonathan Miller (Side A), Paxman (Side B), 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - The National Computer Conference, 1985, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Terry Gross, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Alan Bennet-Diaries 1980-1990, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Melvyn Bragg (Side A), Psychiatrist's Chair (Side B), 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - 31516 (Box 11)
    - Pioneers of Computing, T. H. Wilkinson, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Pioneers of Computing, T. H. Wilkinson, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Ringo Starr & wife of Lennon Beatles, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - 6/20/1986, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Terry [Illegible], 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Stort Story KQED, 11/18/2000, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - [Illegible] (Side A), National Service (Side B), 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Paxman (Side A), Bragg (Side B), 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - John Cornwell-The Choice (Side A), 1999, Melvyn Bragg-Prayer (Side B), 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Paxman Demo, 2000, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Paxman, 2001 (Side A), Fergal Keane-Jews (Side B), 2001, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - F. L. Wright #2, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - F. L. Wright #3, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - F. L. Wright #4, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - F. L. Wright #5, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
    - Unlabeled, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 11)
  - Certificate-Membership-Illinois Presidents Council (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Certificate-Appointment-Foreign Member, Royal Swedish Academy of Engineering Sciences, Stockholm, Sweden, 1986. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Certificate-Life Member-The University of Illinois Alumni Association, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Diploma- Honorary Degree-University of Illinois, 1991 (with photographs) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Diploma-Wright Branch Junior College, 1951 (with photographs) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Diploma-Roosevelt High School, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Diploma-University of Illinois, Master of Arts, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Diploma-Honorary Degree-The University of Dundee, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Photograph (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Certificate-Alexander Technique Lessons, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Honorary Degree Ceremony, Universitat Louvain, Belgium, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Speech and program, Honorary Degree, University of Grenoble, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Election to Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Diploma-Honorary Degree-The University of Waterloo, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Election to National Academy of Engineering, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Photograph-Haugan School, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Photograph (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Certificate-Admission to High School, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - B. Bolzano Gold Medal for Merit in the Field of Mathematical Sciences, Academy of Sciencesof the Czech Republic, March 1994. (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2008-184
  - Notebooks containing GG publications 1993-99, 1997-, 1995-96, 1993-94
    - Gene Golub Publications: COPIES 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Gene Golub Publications: COPIES 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Gene Golub Publications: COPIES 1997— (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Gene Golub Publications: COPIES 1993-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Notebooks containing GG publications 1976-80, 1973-75, 1961-69, 1970-72
    - Gene Golub Publications: COPIES 1961-1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Gene Golub Publications: COPIES 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Gene Golub Publications: COPIES 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Gene Golub Publications: COPIES 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Assorted materials – some publications, articles, correspondence, photographs
    - Inverse Eigenvalue Problems: Theory, Algorithms, Applications (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Basic Earth Imaging (Version 2.1): A Living Document (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Spring Quarter 02-03 Lecture Notes (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Suarjana, Made PhD Thesis 12/93 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Lecture Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Photographs (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - An Iterative Block Lanczos Method for the Solution of Large Sparse Symmetric Eigenproblems by Richard Underwood May 1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - P. Henrici Numerical Math with the Pocket Calculator (pt.1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Gatlinburg X (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Golub- Kent 1 Chebyshev Stuff (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Photographs of Gene Golub (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - An Interview With Gene Golub OH XXX 22& 23 October, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Data Analysis and the Singular Value Decomposition Lecture Notes (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - The Generalized Eigenvalue Problem for Non-Square Pencils Using A Minimal Perturbation Approach (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - The Filter Algorithm For Solving Large-Scale Eigenproblems From Accelerator Simulations, Young Sun March 2003 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Misc. Papers, Notes, Lectures, E-mails (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Notebooks containing GG Masters (publications) 1976-80, 1973-75, 1970-72, 1961-69; 1993-94 daily calendar; 2 other SU publications
    - Gene Golub Publications: MASTERS 1976-1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - 1993-1994 Academic Planner (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Three-Dimensional Filtering: Environmental soundings image enhancement December 20, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - EE364: Introduction to Convex Optimization with Engineering Applications Winter 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - A Block Lanczos Method to Compute the Singular Values and Corresponding Singular Vectors of a Matrix October 1977 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Gene Golub Publications: MASTERS 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Gene Golub Publications: MASTERS 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Gene Golub Publications: MASTERS 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Notebooks containing GG publications 1990-92, 1987-89, 1981-86; 2 GG publications; Notebook for SC336 Winter 1999
  - Notebooks containing GG Masters (publications) 1992-93, 1990-91, 1987-89, 1981-86; GG's Ph.D. thesis 1959
  - Assorted files, photographs, certificates
    - Unfoldered Material (Box 7)
    - CS 137 Binder (Box 7)
    - BIT Abstract (Box 7)
    - Brief Biography of Professor Golub (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Honorary Degrees – Leuven (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - FJ Chair – Personal (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Gene H. Golub – Pictures (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Pictures (Formers Students, etc) (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Gene's 60th Birthday (1992) (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Retirement (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Scholarship Fund (Franz Hohn and JP Nash) (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Golub's Sigene 60th Celebra (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Dell Contract (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Stamp Collection (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Department of the Navy 1989 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - IMA Membership (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Research Activities of G.H. Golub (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Photos: A. S. Householder and G. Golub 6/93 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Awards 1993 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Honorary Degree: University of Illinois (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - NASA Badge (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - American Mathematical Society (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - IVA: Royal Swedish Academy of Engineering Sciences (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Commencement 1991 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Japan Prize Nomination (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Grenobel, France (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Unlabeled (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Additional Unfoldered Material (Box 7)
  - Notebooks (2) of GG chron correspondence; Assorted GG writings and other class items
  - On the Solution of Large, Structured Linear Complementarity Problems: III (Box 9)
  - Shape Reconstruction from Measured Moments (Box 9)
  - Golub 138 (Box 9)
  - Chapter 2: Linear Systems (Box 9)
  - CS 237 Fall '88-‘89 (Box 9)
  - Stanford Computer Forum Binder (Box 9)
  - "World Level" Diploma for Hall of Fame for Engineering, Science, and Technology (Box 9)
  - University of Illinois Honor Awards Convocation (Box 9)
  - "Adaptive Lanczos Methods for Recursive Condition Estimation," in Arkwright transparency film box (Box 9)
  - Singular Value Decomp. Talk (Box 9)
  - A QR-Like SVD Algorith for a Product/Quotient of Several Matrices (Box 9)
  - CS 237 Binder (Box 9)
  - Intr Sci Comp Binder (Box 9)
  - A Prelude to Progress in Scientific Computing (Box 9)
  - Solution of Biharmonic Equations with Applications to Radar Imaging (Box 9)
  - Matrices, Moments, and Quadrature with Applications (Box 9)
  - Gene Golub CS 339 Spring Quarter 2002-03 Lecture Notes (Box 9)
  - 2 Unlabeled CDs (Box 9)
  - Compstat Books of Posters and Abstracts CD (Box 9)
  - Scientific Report Department of Electrical Engineering ESAT 1999-2000 CD (Box 9)
  - Fields Medallists' Lectures CD (Box 9)
  - Maxima Simulation Data CD (Box 9)
  - 6 VHS Tapes (Box 9)
  - Box of Floppy Discs4 (Box 9)
  - Unlabeled (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - CS 137 Spring ‘90 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Numerical Algorithms: Log (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Chew, Khien M. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Unlabeled (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - CS 237 A Autumn ;'89 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Unlabeled (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Unlabeled (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Georlitie Problem (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Unlabeled (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Unlabeled (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Geraub, Pablo A (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Homotopy Method for General Lambda Matrix Problems (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Phone Calls/Nos. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Dietrich, G (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - CS 337B (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Departmental Matters (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Unlabeled (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Karner, Christopher J (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Stefanski, Pawel A (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Inner/Outer Talk (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Inverse Sturm-Liouville Problem (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Unlabeled (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Transparencies (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Stark, Luc J (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Unlabeled (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - 60 Long P's .25 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - NA/Stat Lectures (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Unlabeled (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Research Notes (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Vogel/NM (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Linear Algebra (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - L Geodetic (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - CS 237 A and B (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Unlabeled (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Unlabeled (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Ph. D Qualifying Exams (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Math 2030 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Stable Polygon Reconstruction From Moments With Applications (Box 11)
  - Unlabeled (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Unlabeled (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Unlabeled (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - BAI/Golub (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Unlabeled (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Elhay/Golub/Ram (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Inner/Outer Iterations (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Old Transparencies (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Golub/Sameh/Vivek (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Unlabeled (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - SCCM Presentation – Visiting Commission (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - SCCM Affiliation (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Gander, Martin – Oral Examination / Joseph File (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Slitex Slides for Gene (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Slide Presentation: A history of numerical linear algebra (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - University of York Engineering April 1-4 1996 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Linkoping Lecture (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Unlabeled (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Gear, CW (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - J Zhang (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - G Yuan (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - G Ye (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Vandershasten (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Sun (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Unlabeled (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - CS 237 A (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - CS 137 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - CS 137 B (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Unlabeled (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - CS 135 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Glowinski (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - PCU Factorization (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - CS 137 Winter 68 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Photographs, mouse pad and other miscellany
    - Doctor of Science Degree from The University of Illinois (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Stanford 50 Mousepad (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Photographs from Hong Kong Baptist University from 43rd Commencement and Council Dinner (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - University of Waterloo (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - CS 237C Time Dependent Problems and Difference Methods Spring 1995 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Math 220 Partial Differential Equations, vol. II Fall 1997 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - CS 138 Lecture Notes (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Terror and Exile August 19 to 27, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - A System and Language Environment for Scientific Computing (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - 3D Composite Grids for Flow Computations the grid generation (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Numerical Computation of Unsteady Incompressible Flow in Complex Geometry Using a Composite Multigrid Technique (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Effects of Inhomogeneous Filtering and Buoyant Forcing on the Dynamic Subgrid Scale Model (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Efficient Simulation of Single- and Multi-Species Transport in Groundwater with Local Adaptive Grid Refinement (LAGR) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - NSF- Computational methods in LA using the theory of moments, 11/11/94 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Hiriart-Urruty, J B; Sensitivty analysis of all eigenvalues of a … (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Rank-One Approximation to High Order Tensors (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Towards a Sparse Singular Value Decomposition (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Moments & Statistical Computation (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Lecture Notes and Transparencies (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Lecture Notes and Transparencies (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Lecture Notes and Problems (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Lecture Notes & Transparencies (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Lecture Notes & Transparencies (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Lecture Notes & Transparencies (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Lecture Notes & Transparencies (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Lecture Notes & Transparencies (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Lecture Notes & Transparencies (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Lecture Notes & Transparencies (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Lecture Notes & Transparencies (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Lecture Notes & Transparencies (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Lecture Notes & Transparencies (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Lecture Notes & Transparencies (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Lecture Notes & Transparencies (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Third International Workshop on "TLS and Errors-in-Variables Modeling" (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Morocco/ France September 2001 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous Papers and Pictures (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Manuscripts:
    - Golub/Ortega Book [Binder] (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Gene Golub Publications-Copies [Binder], 2000-2003 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Gene Golub Publications-Copies [Binder], 2000-2003 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Emails and Documents, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Honorary Degree-Rostov State University Russia, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Avishai Furmanski-Family Photographs, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - SIAM Journal on Matrix Analysis and Applications-Dedicated to Gene H. Golub, February 29, 1992 [Book] (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence & Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Oversize materials:
    - Posters (Box 15 os, Folder 1)
    - Matted Art and Awards (Box 15 os, Folder 2)
    - Photographs, Undeveloped Film, Digital Photographs on Compact Disc (Box 16)
    - Photographs, Slides (Box 17)
    - Photographs, Memorabilia, Miscellaneous 3-Dimensional Objects (Box 18)
    - Plaques (Box 19)
    - Poster [Oversize-Rolled] (Box 20 os)
    - Diplomas, certificates, etc. (Box 21 os)